All right. Now you know what you're buyin'.
好了  现在你们验过货了
Let me tell you the price.
我来说说我的要价吧
First... I want outta here.
一  我要离开这儿
Second, I want full custody of my daughter.
二  我要女儿的全部监护权
All right? And her mom can have, like... supervised visits.
她妈妈可以在监督下来探视
But, her stank-ass boyfriend can't come.
但她讨厌的男友不能来
Darnell can't come.
达奈尔不能来
-Darnell's out. -He's out.
-达奈尔不能来  -他不能来
Third, y'all gonna pay for my daughter's whole education.
三  你们要支付我女儿完成整个学业
Best schools. And then I want her to go to college.
最好的学校  然后我要她上大学
Like Harvard. Or Yale. So Ivy league.
哈佛  耶鲁什么的  常青藤学校
Ivy league, yeah. One of them big joints, you know?
没错  大学校  知道吧
And if she can't cut it...
如果她进不去
and her grades start slipping, I need you to white-people that thing.
如果她成绩开始下滑了  我需要你去想办法